Esmond Agharovbokhan.

Ikeja, Lagos State, Nigeria

aghaa0880@gmail.com

07035967785

linkedin.com/in/esmondagharovbokhan-7766a2274

Summary

I am a software developer who has gained several knowledge and experience in recent times. I have been working for more than one year now as a software developer with experience and skills in several web technologies that help create powerful, user-friendly websites. In the past, I have amassed a plethora of skills in various web technologies such as HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap and Tailwind, JavaScript, PHP, ReactJS, and many more. I have also successfully developed the application of a gas ordering system by putting the aforementioned skills into use. I have collaborated with others to work on projects relating to web and app development which makes me not only target-driven but also a team player.

Experience

Software Development Engineer / Tutor

SanerClimes Technology Ltd Jan 2024 - Present (2 months)



Software Developer

Moat Academy for Developers

May 2023 - Feb 2024 (10 months)

Enhanced my comprehension of the React JavaScript framework

Utilized Jira, Trello, and Slack for task management and assignment tracking

Attained foundational knowledge of software development and design principles.

Created modules for a gas ordering system using PHP/MySQL, and performed basic UI design using HTML, CSS, JavaScript / Jquery, and AJAX. Also vast in the Laravel framework, ReactJS

Project Manager

DANEHILL

Feb 2022 - Mar 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Managing and supervising projects on and off sites

Store Manager

Hotel Park Palace Jan 2020 - Nov 2021 (1 year 11 months)



Union Bank of Nigeria Feb 2017 - Mar 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Education

Near East University (NEU)

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business Administration and Management, General Sep 2019 - Jun 2021

Delta State University, Nigeria

Bachelor's degree, Economics Feb 2009 - Oct 2014

Skills

Project Management • Contract Negotiation • Customer Relationship Management (CRM) • HTML5 • JavaScript • PHP • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Laravel • React.js • SQL